// Javascript array quiz

const questions = [
  {
    question: 'What is the index of the first element in an array?',
    options: ['0', '1', '2', '3'],
    answerIndex: 0,
  },
  {
    question: 'What is the index of the last element in an array?',
    options: ['n', 'infinity', "array's length", "array's length - 1"],
    answerIndex: 3,
  },
  {
    question: 'How to add an element to the end of an array?',
    options: ['push', 'unshift', 'pop', 'shift'],
    answerIndex: 0,
  },
  {
    question: 'How to remove an element from the end of an array?',
    options: ['shift', 'pop', 'unshift', 'push'],
    answerIndex: 1,
  },
  {
    question: 'How to add an element to the beginning of an array?',
    options: ['push', 'pop', 'unshift', 'shift'],
    answerIndex: 2,
  },
  {
    question: 'How to remove an element from the beginning of an array?',
    options: ['shift', 'pop', 'unshift', 'push'],
    answerIndex: 0,
  },
  {
    question: 'How to add an element to a specific index of an array?',
    options: ['splice', 'push', 'unshift', 'pop'],
    answerIndex: 0,
  },
  {
    question: 'How to remove an element from a specific index of an array?',
    options: ['splice', 'pop', 'unshift', 'push'],
    answerIndex: 0,
  },
  {
    question: 'How to get a portion of elements from an array?',
    options: ['slice', 'splice', 'pop', 'push'],
    answerIndex: 0,
  },
  {
    question: 'How to join two arrays?',
    options: ['concat', 'join', 'splice', 'push'],
    answerIndex: 0,
  },
  {
    question: 'How to modify order of an array',
    options: ['order', 'sort', 'splice', 'filter'],
    answerIndex: 1,
  },
  {
    question: 'How to filter an array',
    options: ['filter', 'reverse', 'sort', 'order'],
    answerIndex: 0,
  },
];

export default questions;
